Class of 1948 Records, 1944-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1948 Records
1944-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1948.
RG 80 UUID:21081903-49db-45ee-a4db-4acbc7d5c62b
6 boxes (3.1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1948.
The Class of 1948 was the seventieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1948 Records, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1948, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, financial information, class surveys, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1948 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Photographs 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Speaker 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 3)
- Constitution and By-laws 1983 (Box 2161, Folder 4)
- Correspondence with Alumnae House 1981-1987 (Box 2161, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1944-1945 (Box 2161, Folder 6)
- Fundraising Appeal undated (Box 2161, Folder 7)
- General 1944-1945 (Box 2161, Folder 8)
- Groups 1944-1948 (Box 2161, Folder 9)
- Hoop Rolling 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom 1947 (Box 2161, Folder 13)
- Last Sing 1948 (Box 2161, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1958-2003 (Box 2161, Folder 15)
- List of Deceased Alumnae 1987 (Box 2161, Folder 16)
- Officers 1944-1948 (Box 2161, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1949-1968 (Box 2161, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1973-1978 (Box 2161, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1973-1978 (Box 2161, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1983 (Box 2161, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 2161, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1993 (Box 2162, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1998-2002 (Box 2162, Folder 2)
- Reunion Photographs undated (Box 2162, Folder 3)
- Senior Prom 1948 (Box 2162, Folder 4)
- Songs undated (Box 2162, Folder 5)
- Sophomore Carnival 1946 (Box 2162, Folder 6)
- Class Supper 1948 (Box 2162, Folder 7)
- Class Surveys A-J 1981-1983 (Box 2162, Folder 8)
- Class Surveys K-R 1981-1983 (Box 2162, Folder 9)
- Class Surveys S-Z 1981-1983 (Box 2162, Folder 10)
- Treasurer 1952, 1983-1993 (Box 2162, Folder 11)
- Treasurer-Attempt to get tax exempt status 1993-1995 (Box 2162, Folder 12)
- Treasurer-Class Dues 1951-1973 (Box 2162, Folder 13)